A Guide to the Records of the Division of Motion Picture Censorship, 1926-1968
Library of Virginia
- Licenses regular and non-regular, 1954-1965
  - Licenses (Regular), CS20601-CS20800, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS20801-CS21000, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS21001-CS21200, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS21201-CS21400, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS21401-CS21600, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS21601-CS21676, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS21677-CS21819, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS21820-CS22000, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS22001-CS22200, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS22201-CS22319, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS22320-22400, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS22401-CS22600, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS22601-CS22699, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS22700-CS22800, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS22801-CS23000, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS23001-CS23200, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS23201-CS23400, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS23401-CS23600, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS23601-CS23800, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS23801-CS23899, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS23900-CS24000, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS24001-CS24119, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS24120-CS24200, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS24201-CS24319, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS24320-CS24400, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS24401-CS24600, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS24601-CS24689, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS24690-CS24800, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS24801-CS25000, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS25001-CS25130, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS25131-CS25200, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS25201-CS25299, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS25300-CS25400, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS25401-CS25600, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS25601-CS25719, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS25720-CS25800, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS25801-CS26000, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26001-CS26099, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26100-CS26200, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26201-CS26299, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26300-CS26400, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26401-CS26529, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26530-CS26600, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26601-CS26800, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26801-CS26919, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS26920-CS27000, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS27001-CS27200, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS27201-CS27400, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS27401-CS27600, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS27601-CS27800, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS27801-CS28000, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS28001-CS28175, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 99434-99600, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 99601-99800, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 99801-100000, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 100001-100200, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 100201-100400, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 100401-100600, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 100601-100800, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 100801-101000, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 101001-101200, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 101201-101400, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 101401-101600, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 101601-101800, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 101801-102000, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 102001-102200, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 102201-102400, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 102401-102600, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 102601-102800, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 102801-103000, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 103001-103200, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 103201-103400, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 103401-103600, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 103601-103800, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 103801-103999, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 104000-104200, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 104201-104400, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 104401-104600, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 104601-104800, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 104801-105000, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 105001-105200, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 105201-105400, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 105401-105600, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 105601-105800, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 105801-106000, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 106001-106200, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 106201-106400, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 106401-106600, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 106601-106800, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 106801-107000, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 107001-107200, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 107201-107400, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 107401-107600, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 107601-107800, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 107801-107999, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 108000-108200, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 108201-108400, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 108401-108539, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 108540-108600, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 108601-108800, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 108801-109000, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 109001-109129, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 109130-109200, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 109201-109400, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 109401-109600, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 109601-109800, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 109801-109919, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 109920-110000, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 110001-110200, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 110201-110299, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 110300-110400, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 110401-110600, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 110601-110800, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 110801-111000, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 111001-111200, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 111201-111400, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 111401-111600, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 111601-111800, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 111801-112000, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 112001-112200, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 112201-112400, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 112401-112600, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 112601-112800, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 112801-113000, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 113001-113200, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 113201-113400, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 113401-113600, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 113601-113800, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 113801-114000, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 114001-114200, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 114201-114400, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 114401-114600, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 114601-114799, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 114800-115000, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 115001-115200, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 115201-115400, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 115401-115600, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 115601-115800, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 115801-116000, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 116001-116200, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 116201-116400, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 116401-116600, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 116601-116800, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 116801-117000, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Non-Regular), 117001-117114, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Index to licenses and applications, 1947-1965
  This series contains 4x6 index cards that serve as an index to the non-regular licenses and the license applications. The index provides the motion picture title, dat of license or application, studio releasing the film and serial number. The pink index cards provide notations about the status of the film, such as, whether a seal has been issued for a film, whether the film was eliminated or "rejected in toto", meaning it could not be shown in the state, and the conditional approval of a film with the seal of Virginia issued at a later date. The index does not apply to the regular licenses.
  - Index to licenses and applications, A-AM, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, AN-AR, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, AS-AW, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, B-BAY, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, BE, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, BI-BLO, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, BLU-BOY, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, BR-BY, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Index to licenses and applications, C-CAV, 1947-1965 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, CE-COL, 1947-1965 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, COM-CROS, 1947-1965 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, CROW-CY, 1947-1965 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, D-DEM, 1947-1965 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, DEN-DIC, 1947-1965 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, DIE-DY, 1947-1965 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, E, 1947-1965 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, F-FEU, 1947-1965 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, FEV-FL, 1947-1965 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, FOA-FOY, 1947-1965 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, FRA-FRO, 1947-1965 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, G-GI, 1947-1965 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, GL-GO, 1947-1965 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, GR-GU, 1947-1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Index to licenses and applications, HA, 1947-1965 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, HE-HM, 1947-1965 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, HOA-HOUR, 1947-1965 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, HOUS-HY, 1947-1965 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, I-IN, 1947-1965 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, IP-IW, 1947-1965 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, J, 1947-1965 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, K, 1947-1965 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Index to licenses and applications, L-LA, 1947-1965 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, LE-LI, 1947-1965 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, LO-LU, 1947-1965 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, M-MAM, 1947-1965 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, MAN-MAY, 1947-1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, ME-MI, 1947-1965 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, MOC-MOZ, 1947-1965 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, MU-MY, 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, NA-NIJ, 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, NIK-NUT, 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, OA-ONH, 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, ONI-OZ, 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, PA-PE, 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, PH-POP, 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, POR-PY, 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Index to licenses and applications, Q, 1947-1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, RA-RES, 1947-1965 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, RET-RI, 1947-1965 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, RO-RX, 1947-1965 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, SA, 1947-1965 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, SC-SE, 1947-1965 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, SH-SID, 1947-1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, SIE-SL, 1947-1965 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Index to licenses and applications, SM-SO, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, SP-STOP, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, STOR-SUN, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, SUR-SYN, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, TA-TEL, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, TEM-THIR, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, THIS-THU, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, TIA-TON, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Index to licenses and applications, TOO-TRI, 1947-1965 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Index to licenses and applications, TRO-TWO, 1947-1965 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Index to licenses and applications, U, 1947-1965 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Index to licenses and applications, V, 1947-1965 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Index to licenses and applications, WA, 1947-1965 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Index to licenses and applications, WE-WIK, 1947-1965 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Index to licenses and applications, WIL-WIZ, 1947-1965 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Index to licenses and applications, WO-WY, 1947-1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Index to licenses and applications, X-Y-Z, 1947-1965 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Attendance reports for employees, 1958-1965
  This series contains 4x6 index cards that served as attendance forms for imployees of the Division of Motion Picture Censorship. Each card has the name of the employee, day of the week, check mark for when the employee was present or on sick/vacation leave, and the signature of employees.
  Arranged alphabetically by employee.
  - Argabright, Wanda Mae, 1961-1963 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Bevan, Thomas, 1958-1960 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Bevan, Thomas, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Bevan, Thomas, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Bevan, Thomas, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Bevan, Thomas, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Bevan, Thomas, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Bevan, Thomas, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Hagen, Garlan, 1958-1960 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Hagen, Garlan, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Hagen, Garlan, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Hagen, Garlan, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Hagen, Garlan, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Hagen, Garlan, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Hagen, Garlan, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Hagen, Garlan 1966 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Lillian, 1958-1960 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Lillian, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Lillian, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Jones, Lillian, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Jones, Lillian, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Jones, Lillian, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Jones, Lillian, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Moore, Peggy, 1958-1960 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Moore, Peggy, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Moore, Peggy, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Moss, Peggy Moore, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Moss, Peggy, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Moss, Peggy, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Moss, Peggy, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Ross, Phyllis M., 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Ross, Phyllis M., 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Ross, Phyllis M., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Tucker, Leonard, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Tucker, Leonard, 1959-1960 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Tucker, Leonard, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Tucker, Leonard, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Tucker, Leonard, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Tucker, Leonard, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Tucker, Leonard, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Theater and Inspector Listings, 1959-1965
  This series consists of 4x6 index cards giving an alphabetical listing of movie theaters and a separate listing for the name and address of inspectors along with the names of the theaters they were responsible for monitoring. The movie theaters are organized by location of county, city or town. The index cards have notations for "Negro" inspectores and/or "Negro" owned theaters. The cards are divided into active (white color cards) and inactive (pink color cards) cards. There is a separate listing of index cards for inspectors of drive-in theaters.
  Arranged alphabetically by location.
  - Theater listings, A-E, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Theater listings, F-M, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Theater listings, N-P, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Theater listings, R-T, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Theater listings, A-K (Closed), 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Theater listings, L-Y (Closed), 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Inspector listings, B-K (Indoor theaters), 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Inspector listings, L-W (Indoor theaters), 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Inspector listings, A-K (Drive-in theaters), 1959-1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Inspector listings, L-W (Drive-in theaters), 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Listing of Film Titles, 1928-1957
  This series provides a typed listing of movie titles, seal numbers, and notations of films eliminated or approved for viewing within the state. Some of the listings supply only the date, movie title, serial number and name of the studio releasing the film.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - A-Z, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - A-W, 1929-2930 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - A-Y, 1930-1933 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - A-Z, 1932-1938 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - A-Y, 1938-1941 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - A-Y, 1942-1944 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - A-W, 1945-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - A-Y, 1947-1950 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - A-Z, 1948-1952 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - A-W, 1953-1955 (Bulk 1953-1954) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - A-Z, 1953-1955 (Bulk 1955) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - A-Z, 1956-1957 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - A-Z, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Financial records, 1949-1965
  This series consists of five volumes, one tablet, and a selection of financial reports that are Daily Billings (the form is entitled Film Record), which provide an overview of the financial housekeeping of the agency. There are three volumes entitled Cash Receipts dated 1950-1966 that provide an accounting ledger format with columns for dates of transactions, studio names and assigned license number, fees for original and duplicate licenses, news reels charges and substitute seal fee, along with totals for all columns.
  There are two volumes entitles Disbursements dated 1949-1950 that are organized in similar format to the Cash Receipts. The columns in these two volumes are identified follows: salaries, wages, repairs, maintenance service contract, travel, transportation, communications, printing, other expenses, office supplies, photographic, supplies, other supplies, office equipment, fire insurance, workmen's compensation, surety insurance, technical subscriptions, and capital outlay.
  The one tablet entitled Office Cash Vouchers is dated 1962 and is an accounting booklet for the office petty cash fund. The column headings in this tablet are for date of transaction, nature of disbursement, amount paid, totals and signatures for those authorized to approve payment, certification for the correct reimbursement and the checker of the transaction.
  The Daily Billings or Film Record are dated 1960-1965 and provide and insightful account of the amount of fees generated by charges applied to studios for original and duplicate prints and the seal of issuance. The contains the title of the movie, studio releasing film, number of reels, total footage amount, print number, original seal number, duplicate seal number, substitute seal number and total of fees collected. Some reports have adding machine tabulations attached to them.
  - Cash receipts (1 v.), 1950-1955 (Box 43)
  - Cash receipts (1 v.), 1955-1963 (Box 43)
  - Cash receipts (1 v.), 1963-1966 (Box 43)
  - Disbursements (1 v.), 1949-1960 (Box 43)
  - Disbursements (1 v.), 1960-1966 (Box 43)
  - Office Cash Voucher booklet (1 v.), 1962 (Box 43)
  - Daily billing, 1960 July (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Daily billing, 1960 August (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Daily billing, 1960 September (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Daily billing, 1960 October (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Daily billing, 1960 November (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Daily billing, 1960 December (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Daily billing, 1961 January (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Daily billing, 1961 February (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Daily billing, 1961 March (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Daily billing, 1961 April (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Daily billing, 1961 May (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Daily billing, 1961 June (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Daily billing, 1961 July (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Daily billing, 1961 August (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Daily billing, 1961 September (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Daily billing, 1961 October (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Daily billing, 1961 November (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Daily billing, 1961 December (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Daily billing, 1962 January (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Daily billing, 1962 February (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Daily billing, 1962 March (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Daily billing, 1962 April (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Daily billing, 1962 May (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Daily billing, 1962 June (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Daily billing, 1962 July (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Daily billing, 1962 August (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Daily billing, 1962 September (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Daily billing, 1962 October (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Daily billing, 1962 November (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Daily billing, 1962 December (Box 44, Folder 30)